Love's Enduring Promise is a drama, romance, western
film directed by Michael Landon Jr..
In the 1800s frontier, Missie Davis is a bright and beautiful schoolteacher whose
love for the prairie is matched only by her passion for books.
When Missie encounters Grant, a handsome New England railroad executive,
she feels as though she's met a hero from one of her novels.
Missie Davis, played by January Jones.
Willie LaHaye / Nate, played by Logan Bartholomew.
Clark Davis, played by Dale Midkiff.
Marty Davis, played by Katherine Heigl.
Aaron Davis, played by Kesun Loder.
Arnie Davis, played by Logan Arens.
Love's Enduring Promise is a 2004 made-for-television Christian
drama film based on a series of books by Janette Oke.
The film is the second in the Love Comes Softly series of television movies on Hallmark Channel that includes Love Comes Softly (2003), Love's Long Journey (2005), Love's Abiding Joy (2006), Love's Unending Legacy
(2007), Love's Unfolding Dream, Love Takes Wing (2009), and Love Finds a Home produced for Hallmark by Larry Levinson Productions(2009), as well as the 2011 prequels Love Begins and Love's Everlasting Courage.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, sequel,
pioneer women, 19th century, christian faith.
The tone is emotional.